<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<application-update>
  <update-info-xml-url>
    http://www.helixoft.com/files/free/multiline-search/update.xml
  </update-info-xml-url>

  <release latest="yes">
    <version>
      <major>1</major>
      <minor>5</minor>
      <build></build>
      <revision></revision>
    </version>
    <date>
      <day>09</day>
      <month>06</month>
      <year>2014</year>
    </date>
    <whats-new>
      <![CDATA[
        1. NEW: Added new find options: Ignore leading whitespaces, Ignore trailing whitespaces, Ignore all whitespaces. This way you have more flexibility with indented text, inline multiple whitespaces, etc. See the help for more details.
        2. NEW: Added a short help (user guide).
        3. CHANGE: Improved resizing. You can now drag the splitter and resize Find what and Replace with text boxes.
        4. FIX: Ctrl+A in Find what and Replace with text boxes didn't work.
]]>
    </whats-new>
    <download-url>
      http://visualstudiogallery.msdn.microsoft.com/699CE302-B0D4-4083-BE0E-1682E873CEBF
    </download-url>
    <home-url>
      http://visualstudiogallery.msdn.microsoft.com/699CE302-B0D4-4083-BE0E-1682E873CEBF
    </home-url>
    <buy-url>
      http://visualstudiogallery.msdn.microsoft.com/699CE302-B0D4-4083-BE0E-1682E873CEBF
    </buy-url>
    <release-notes-url>
      http://visualstudiogallery.msdn.microsoft.com/699CE302-B0D4-4083-BE0E-1682E873CEBF
    </release-notes-url>
  </release>


  <release latest="no">
    <version>
      <major>6</major>
      <minor>7</minor>
      <build></build>
      <revision></revision>
    </version>
    <date>
      <day>14</day>
      <month>03</month>
      <year>2014</year>
    </date>
    <whats-new>
      <![CDATA[
       1. NEW: Added additional keyboard shortcuts for cut, copy and paste - Shift+Del, Ctrl+Ins and Shift+Ins in WYSIWYG comment editor.
       2. CHANGE: Improved Help&Manual output for the latest H&M versions (show TOC when particular topic is loaded with direct URL, fixed newlines in code examples).
       3. CHANGE: Improved performance of comment editing in some projects that reference many third-party assemblies.
       4. FIX: Sometimes, a missing comment was not inherited from overridden/implemented member in a referenced third-party assembly.
       5. FIX: When IE 10 or higher was installed, double/triple-click didn't select whole word/sentence in WYSIWYG comment editor. Moreover, the word selection is improved now, it works as in VS editor. A word can contain an underscore '_' character and it doesn't contain a trailing space.
       6. FIX: In very rare cases, when you clicked inside WYSIWYG comment editor, the caret was set to a wrong position.
       7. FIX: In WYSIWYG comment editor, when a text selection contained a text of various colors, it was impossible to change its properties, e.g. change it to a bulleted list.
       8. FIX: Application could crash when pasting a text copied from MS Word (and maybe some other applications too) into WYSIWYG comment editor.
       9. FIX: The language selected by a user in local HTML documentation was not retained in Chrome browser. Moreover, the default selected language is C# and not VB now. This can be changed in a generated config file.
      10. FIX: In docx  output, multiple sub-classes were indented incorrectly in the Inheritance Hierarchy.
      11. FIX: The Inheritance Hierarchy was not generated for some classes in some cases.
]]>
    </whats-new>
    <download-url>
      http://www.helixoft.com/common/product-downloads.html
    </download-url>
    <home-url>
      http://www.helixoft.com/vsdocman/overview.html
    </home-url>
    <buy-url>
      http://www.helixoft.com/common/buy-helixoft-products.html
    </buy-url>
    <release-notes-url>
      http://www.helixoft.com/vsdocman/release-notes.html
    </release-notes-url>
  </release>


  </application-update>